{
  "questions": [ 
      {
           "question": "What does SQL stand for?",
           "answers": ["Strong Question Language", "Structured Question Language","Structured Query Language"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which SQL statement is used to extract data from a database?",
           "answers": ["SELECT", "EXTRACT","GET"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "Which SQL statement is used to update data in a database?",
           "answers": ["Modify", "Save as", "Update", "Save"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which SQL statement is used to delete data from a database?",
           "answers": ["Remove", "Delete", "Collapse"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Which SQL statement is used to insert new data in a database?",
           "answers": ["Insert Into", "Add","Add new"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "With SQL, how do you select a column named 'FirstName' from a table named 'Persons'?",
           "answers": ["SELECT Persons.FirstName", "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "With SQL, how do you select all the columns from a table named 'Persons'?",
           "answers": ["SELECT Persons", "SELECT [all] FROM Persons", "SELECT * FROM Persons"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "What is variable declaration?",
           "answers": ["instantiating a class", "retrieving a return value from a method", "creating a primitive type variable", "stating a variable type and name"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "What is the number 5 in this code: System.out.println(\"amount: \"+5);",
           "answers": ["a constant", "a variable", "a literal", "an object"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following primitive types can only have two possible values?",
           "answers": ["byte", "char", "boolean", "short"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following represents \"or\" in Java logic?",
           "answers": ["+=", "&&", "!", "||"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following ends an infinite for loop?",
           "answers": ["stop();", "end;", "break;", "exit();"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
      
     ]
 }
